const STORE = [
  {
    question: "What street is Bob’s restaurant on?",
    answers: ["Main Street","Lakeview Avenue","Ocean Avenue","Elm Street"],
    rightAnswer: "Ocean Avenue"
  },
  {
    question: "What town do the kids go trick or treating UNSUPERVISED for Halloween?",
    answers: ["King's Head Island","Highland Park", "Ridgewood Meadows","Short Hills"],
    rightAnswer: "King's Head Island"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Louise’s favorite toy?",
    answers: ["Pikachu", "Mochi Puni", "Kuchi Kopi","Teddy Ruxpin"],
    rightAnswer: "Kuchi Kopi"
  }, {
    question: "What is the subject matter of Tina’s short stories?",
    answers: ["Crime Mysteries","Urban Fantasy","Erotic Friend Fiction","Space Wizards"],
    rightAnswer: "Erotic Friend Fiction"
  }, {
    question: "Who does Tina have a crush on?",
    answers: ["Jimmy Pesto Jr.","Rudy","Henry Haber","Logan"],
    rightAnswer: "Jimmy Pesto Jr."
  }, {
    question: "What other boy does Jimmy Jr’s wrestle with?",
    answers: ["Regular-Sized Rudy","Zeke","Darrell","Large Tommy"],
    rightAnswer: "Zeke"
  }, {
    question: "What was the name of Linda’s rock band? ",
    answers: ["The Bangles","Middle Aged Moms","Hot Flash","The Tatas"],
    rightAnswer: "The Tatas"
  }, {
    question: "Who was the murderer in Linda’s dinner theater mystery?",
    answers: ["The Lonely Morgue Owner","The Tree","Teddy","The Butler"],
    rightAnswer: "The Lonely Morgue Owner"
  }, {
    question: "What is the name of Mr Fischoeder’s brother?",
    answers: ["Gerald","Felix","Monty","Rupert"],
    rightAnswer: "Felix"
  }, {
    question: "Which of these is NOT the name of one of Bob’s Burger’s of the Day?",
    answers: ['New Bacon-ings','Bob’s New Hope Burger','The Child Molester (Comes with Candy!)','Last of the Mo-Jicama'],
    rightAnswer: "Bob’s New Hope Burger "
  }
]
